<Namespace Name="System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection">
  <Metadata><Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="b482f98a5c4316a191cd9beb8d2d226874520920" /><Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="88014e1c5440e3df4f66ef04393854d15b1fd534" /><Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="MT" /><Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="ja-JP" /><Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="09/05/2019" /><Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="70472808" /></Metadata><Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="31124-101"><see cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection" /> 名前空間は、アプリケーションの拡張保護を使用した認証のサポートを提供します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="31124-101">The <see cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection" /> namespace provides support for authentication using extended protection for applications.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="31124-102">統合 Windows 認証 (IWA) の設計では、一部の資格情報チャレンジ応答をユニバーサルにすることができます。つまり、これらを再利用または転送できます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="31124-102">The design of Integrated Windows Authentication (IWA) allows for some credential challenge responses to be universal, meaning they can be re-used or forwarded.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="31124-103">この特定の設計機能が必要でない場合は、少なくともターゲット固有の情報を使用してチャレンジ応答を構築し、チャネル固有の情報を使用することをお勧めします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="31124-103">If this particular design feature is not needed then the challenge responses should be constructed with, at minimum, target specific information and, at best, also some channel specific information.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="31124-104">これにより、サービスは拡張保護を提供して、資格情報チャレンジ応答にサービス固有の情報 (サービスプロバイダー名または SPN) と、必要に応じてチャネル固有の情報 (チャネルバインディングトークンまたは CBT) を含めることができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="31124-104">Services can then provide extended protection to ensure that credential challenge responses contain service specific information (a Service Provider Name or SPN) and, if necessary, channel specific information (a channel binding token or CBT).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="31124-105">資格情報の交換でこの情報を使用すると、不適切に取得された可能性がある資格情報チャレンジ応答の悪意のある使用からサービスを保護することができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="31124-105">With this information in the credential exchanges, services are able to better protect against malicious use of credential challenge responses that might have been improperly obtained.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="T:System.Net.TransportContext" />
    <altmember cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection.Configuration" />
  </Docs>
</Namespace>