<Namespace Name="System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement">
  <Metadata><Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="1b0a20a66c92ce57cb601479515871256ae29cdc" /><Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="355778a8154b2dab885accd76cc040b19ea80e32" /><Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="MT" /><Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="ja-JP" /><Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="03/03/2020" /><Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="78242692" /></Metadata><Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="e2d62-101"><see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /> 名前空間は、複数のプリンシパル ストアにわたって、ユーザー、コンピューター、グループのセキュリティ プリンシパルに同じ方法でアクセスして操作できる名前空間です。Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS)、Active Directory ライトウェイト ディレクトリ サービス (AD LDS)、および Machine SAM (MSAM) です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-101">The <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /> namespace provides uniform access and manipulation of user, computer, and group security principals across the multiple principal stores: Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS), and Machine SAM (MSAM).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-102"><see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /> は、<see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /> 名前空間とは独立してディレクトリ オブジェクトを管理します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-102"><see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /> manages directory objects independent of the <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /> namespace.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-103">管理されたディレクトリサービスアプリケーションは、<xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement> API を利用して、ユーザー、コンピューター、およびグループのプリンシパルの管理を簡略化できます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-103">Managed directory services applications can take advantage of the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement> API to simplify management of user, computer and group principals.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-104">以前にストアまたは長いコードに関する複雑な知識を必要としていたソリューションでは、ユーザーが属するすべてのグループの検索などが、<xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement> API を使用して数行のコードで実行されます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-104">Solutions that previously required intricate knowledge of the store or lengthy code, such as finding all groups to which a user belongs, are accomplished in a few lines of code with the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement> API.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-105"><xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement> API では、次の機能を使用できます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-105">The following features are available on the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement> API:</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-106">セキュリティプリンシパルの作成や更新などの基本的なディレクトリ操作が簡略化されています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-106">Basic directory operations such as creating and updating security principals is simplified.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-107">アプリケーションでは、これらの操作を実行するために、基になるストアに関する知識が少なくなります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-107">The application requires less knowledge of the underlying stores to perform these operations.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-108">アプリケーションでは、オブジェクトモデルを拡張して、新しい種類のディレクトリオブジェクトを含めることができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-108">Applications can extend the object model to include new types of directory objects.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-109">ユーザーアカウントの有効化と無効化など、アカウント管理タスクが簡略化されています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-109">Account management tasks, such as enabling and disabling a user account, are simplified.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-110">複数ストアのサポートにより、Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS)、Active Directory ライトウェイトディレクトリサービス (AD LDS)、コンピューター SAM (MSAM) の各データベース内のグループオブジェクトに、さまざまな種類のストアのメンバーを含めることができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-110">Cross-store support allows group objects in the Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS), and Machine SAM (MSAM) databases to contain members from different types of stores.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-111"><xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.PrincipalSearcher> クラスで利用できるサンプル検索を使用してクエリを実行すると、アプリケーションはプリンシパルオブジェクトのプロパティを設定し、選択したストアで、一致するプロパティ値を含む他のオブジェクトを検索できます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-111">Query by example searching, available on the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.PrincipalSearcher> class, enables applications to set properties on a principal object and search the selected store for other objects that contain matching property values.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-112">コンピューター、ユーザー、およびグループのプリンシパルオブジェクトに対する検索の強化により、アプリケーションは、選択したストアで一致するプリンシパルオブジェクトを検索できます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-112">Enhanced search on computer, user and group principal objects enables applications to search the selected store for matching principal objects.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-113">グループプリンシパルオブジェクトで使用できる再帰検索を使用すると、アプリケーションはグループを再帰的に検索し、リーフノードであるプリンシパルオブジェクトのみを返すことができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-113">Recursive search, available on the group principal object, enables applications to search a group recursively and return only principal objects that are leaf nodes.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-114">コンピューター SAM、AD DS、および AD LS ストアに対する資格情報の検証が簡略化されています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-114">Credential validation against the Machine SAM, AD DS, and AD LS stores is simplified.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-115">高速同時実行バインド (FSB) 機能を使用すると、接続速度が向上します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-115">Connections speeds are increased by using the Fast Concurrent Bind (FSB) feature when available.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="e2d62-116">接続キャッシュは、使用されるポートの数を減らします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-116">Connection caching decreases the number of ports used.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" />
    <related type="Article" href="https://docs.microsoft.com/previous-versions/bb384379(v=vs.90)"><span data-ttu-id="e2d62-117">System.directoryservices 名前空間の概要</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="e2d62-117">System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement Namespace Overview</span></span></related>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>